// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
  numb: 1,
  question: "Python is an",
  answer: "All the above",
  options: [
    " interpreted, high-level, general-purpose programming language",
    "object-oriented programming language",
    "procedural, functional, structured, and reflective programming language",
    "All the above"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 2,
  question: "Which of the following is a correct program to print Hello World as output ?",
  answer: "print('Hello, World!')",
  options: [
    "print('Hello, World!')",
    "printf('Hello, World!')",
    "console('Hello, World!')",
    "put('Hello, World!')"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 3,
  question: "Which of the following is considered as comment in Python ?",
  answer: "Both the above",
  options: [
    "# this is a comment",
    "''' this is a comment'''",
    "Both the above",
    "<< this is a comment"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 4,
  question: "Which of the following commands will create a list (multiple answers allowed) ?",
  answer: "All of the Above",
  options: [
    "mylist = [1, 2, 3]",
    "mylist = list([1, 2, 3])",
    "mylist = list()",
    "All of the Above"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 5,
  question: "What will be the output produced by following program ?mylist = ['c', 'o', 'd', 'e', 's'] print(len(mylist))",
  answer: "5",
  options: [
    "4",
    "5",
    "Error",
    "None of the above"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 6,
  question: " To shuffle the list say mylist, what function do we use ?",
  answer: "random.shuffle(mylist)",
  options: [
    "random.shuffleList(mylist)",
    "mylist.shuffle()",
    "shuffle(mylist)",
    "random.shuffle(mylist)"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 7,
  question: "What is the output of the following program ?mylist = [10, 20, 5, 30, 15] print(mylist[:-1])",
  answer: "[10, 20, 5, 30]",
  options: [
    "[10, 20, 5, 30]",
    "[10, 20, 5, 30, 15]",
    "[15, 20, 5, 30, 10",
    "Error"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 8,
  question: "What will be the output produced by following program ? mylist = [10, 20, 5, 30, 15] print(mylist * 2)",
  answer: "[10, 20, 5, 30, 15, 10, 20, 5, 30, 15]",
  options: [
    "[20, 30]",
    "[10,5, 30, 15]",
    "[20,10, 60, 30]",
    "[10, 20, 5, 30, 15, 10, 20, 5, 30, 15]"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 9,
  question: "Which of the following is an invalid statement ?",
  answer: " a b c = 1000 2000 3000",
  options: [
    "a_b_c = 1,000,000",
    "a,b,c = 1000, 2000, 3000",
    " a b c = 1000 2000 3000",
    "abc = 1,000,000"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 10,
  question: "Which are the advantages of functions in python ?",
  answer: "All of the Above",
  options: [
    "Reducing duplication of code",
    "Decomposing complex problems into simpler pieces",
    "Reuse of code",
    "All of the Above"
  ]
}
];